thesuburbanmom.com 2019-05-08

# Privacy Policy - TheSuburbanMom

Thank you for visiting the TheSuburbanMom Web site, (“the Site” or “TheSuburbanMom”) and reviewing our Privacy Policy, effective August 1, 2009. TheSuburbanMom is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our many offerings.

**Overview**

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) governs your use of TheSuburbanMom. This Policy describes the information we collect from you and what may happen to that information. For example, this Policy will let you know what information we collect from you; what cookies are and how they are used; how your information is used; who is collecting your information; with whom your information may be shared; what options are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information; how you may use other users’ information; the types of security precautions in place to protect against loss, misuse, or alteration of your information; how TheSuburbanMom protects children’s privacy; and other important information about your online privacy.

Please note that we review our privacy practices from time to time, and that our practices are subject to change. We ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Policy. All amended terms shall be automatically effective after they are posted on the Site.

By visiting the Site, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use or access the Site.

**What Personally Identifiable Information does TheSuburbanMom collect?**

The primary purpose of collecting information from you is to provide you with a safe, smooth, effective, and personalized experience. We will only collect information about you that we consider necessary to achieve this purpose.

Generally, TheSuburbanMom collects information in several ways. Some information is gathered when you register. This includes your name, company name, mailing address, phone number, email address, user name, password and credit card information. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. We also collect personal information when you report a problem, either through the Site’s email, direct mail, or via telephone. We may also ask for personal information at other times, including, but not limited to, when you make payments to TheSuburbanMom. If you contact TheSuburbanMom, we may keep a record of that correspondence. We also may ask you questions in a survey concerning your cleaning business, the answers to which are never associated with any personally identifiable information but are viewed for general customer feedback and satisfaction.

Wherever TheSuburbanMom collects personal information, we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

**What are “cookies” and how does TheSuburbanMom use them?**

Data collection devices, such as “cookies,” are used to store, and sometimes track, information about you. Generally, these cookies help provide personalized services and promote trust and safety. A cookie is a small file containing a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and placed on your computer’s hard drive to assist us in providing our services. All pages on the Site where you are prompted to login or that are customizable may require that you accept cookies. Cookies are only read by the server that placed them and are unable to execute any code or virus. Most cookies are “session cookies” and are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. More specifically, we may use cookies to:

Remind us of who you are when you login and to access your account information in order to deliver to you a more personalized service;

Measure your visiting patterns in the aggregate. Aggregate data (data gathered across all user accounts) may be gathered in a non-personally identifiable form to build higher quality, more useful online services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our visitors, such as how long and how often users view certain pages;

Determine your clickstream to our Site;

Better personalize the content that you and other users will see on our Site; and

Collect IP addresses for system administration.

**How does TheSuburbanMom use my information?**

TheSuburbanMom uses your information to provide you with a customized browsing experience. We also may use your personal information to process orders (like submitting your credit card and name and zip code to the credit card processor so your payment goes through properly); resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; respond to your inquiries; detect and protect against error, fraud, or other criminal activity; and enforce our User Agreement. Additionally, we may use your information to contact you about products or services we, an affiliate, or an authorized vendor may all for you.  You may cancel your authorization for this at any time.

**Who is collecting information?**

When you are using the Site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with TheSuburbanMom, affiliates and our authorized vendors, unless we specifically state otherwise or unless we are processing a payment during which information is given to the credit card processor. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than TheSuburbanMom its affiliates and/or authorized vendors, you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer.

Please be advised that TheSuburbanMom advertisers or Web sites that have links on our Site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those Web sites linked to TheSuburbanMom are not covered by this privacy statement.

**With whom does TheSuburbanMom share my information?**

TheSuburbanMom will not disclose your personally identifiable information except with our affiliated companies or authorized vendors, unless we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as those described below.

External Service Providers: Separate services may be offered by third parties, also known as external service providers. If you choose to use these services, disclose information to these parties, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, their privacy policy governs the use of your information. When you inquire about or purchase such services via the Site, TheSuburbanMom shares your information with that external services provider so that they may complete your request.

TheSuburbanMom Employees and Contractors: Some of our employees and contractors are subject to non-disclosure agreements with us. These and other legal restrictions prohibit their use of the information you provide us for any purpose except to facilitate the specific TheSuburbanMom-related operation, unless you explicitly agreed or gave your prior permission to them for additional uses.

Advertisers: If you complete a transaction with an advertiser linked to TheSuburbanMom, the information obtained during your visit to that advertiser, and the information you give, may be provided to the advertiser. Advertisers linked to the Site have separate policy practices for which TheSuburbanMom has no responsibility or liability.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

Other: We may disclose account information where we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating TheSuburbanMom’s policies as specified in the Privacy Policy or User Agreement, violating state or federal law, or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) TheSuburbanMom’s rights or property, other Site users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. TheSuburbanMom may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain and improve our services.

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Policy. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they unlawfully collect from the Site. We use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, however, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

**What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information?**

TheSuburbanMom will contact you if you complete a contact form on the Site, if you sign up for a membership, or if you contact us directly by phone or email. We may also send you email regarding our products and services. Only TheSuburbanMom, or agents working on behalf of TheSuburbanMom, will contact you. TheSuburbanMom may communicate with you via telephone, email, or direct mail. If you do not wish to receive such communications, contact us through the form provided on the Site or write to us at the following address:

TheSuburbanMom  
520 N. Orlando Avenue #44  
Winter Park, FL 32789

Please be advised that if you complete a contact form on the Site, you have expressly agreed to be contacted via telephone by TheSuburbanMom, regardless of whether you are listed on the National or State Do Not Call Registries.

**How may I use other users’ information?**

Recognizing the global nature of the Internet, you agree to comply with all applicable local laws and rules regarding online conduct and privacy, as well as content. Specifically, but not as a limitation, you agree to comply with all applicable laws regarding transmission of technical and personal data exported from the United States or the country in which you reside.

Spam. We do not tolerate spam. You are not licensed to add us or any registered user to your mail (email or physical mail) list without his or her affirmative consent. You are not licensed to use spam in promoting TheSuburbanMom.

**What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?**

Whenever TheSuburbanMom handles your personal information, we take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant User Agreement and this Policy. Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States. We use procedural and mechanical safeguards to protect your personal information against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect your privacy, including encryption. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We cannot, therefore, warrant or ensure the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

As a user of TheSuburbanMom, your TheSuburbanMom account information is password protected so that only you have access to this personal information. We recommend that you do not disclose your password to anyone. TheSuburbanMom will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or unsolicited email. If you choose to share your user name and password or your personal information with third parties, you are responsible for all actions taken with your account and therefore you should review that third party’s privacy policy. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.

**How are children’s privacy protected?**

Persons under the age of 18 (or 21 in some states) are not authorized to use the Site. Those persons are prohibited from submitting any personal information to us. We do not sell or rent personal information about any of our users, regardless of age.

**Additional Information**

Any questions regarding this statement should be directed to jen@thesuburbanmom.com.

This Policy is the sole authorized statement of TheSuburbanMom’s practices with respect to the online collection of personally identifiable information and the usage of such information. Any summaries of this Policy generated by third party software or otherwise shall have no legal effect, are in no way binding upon TheSuburbanMom, shall not be relied upon in substitute for this Policy, and neither supersede nor modify this Policy.

TheSuburbanMom reserves the right to transfer any and all information that we collect from visitors, or that we otherwise collect concerning or in connection with the Site, to a third party in the event of a sale or other transfer of assets or of any portion of our business.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or account information. Please be careful and responsible.
